POP ADRIAN BOGDAN

PHP Internship - Group Five Software

Age 34 from Cluj Napoca, not married - available Anytime

Contact details

Email: popadrianbogdan@yahoo.com

Tel: 0747362453

Address: Henri Barbusse, Cluj Napoca

Professional objective

Although my professional experience is in the field of online and retail sales management, I am currently in the process of a major career change in the direction of web development, mainly focussing on PHP and JAVASCRIPT technologies.

I am self-taught and have acquired basic knowledge of the following: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP-MySql, Phpmyadmin, Symfony Framework and Git.

I am highly motivated and enthusiastic, hardworking always with excellent attention to detail.

Professional experience

Experience by IT Hardware : 5 months departments IT Software : 4 months

Administrative / Logistics: 1 year and 5 months

Sales: 9 years and 4 months

Oct 2016 - present

4 months

PHP Internship - Group Five Software

Cluj-Napoca | IT Software | IT / Telecom

PHP:

-WEB Basics

-PHP introduction

-PHP and Databases

-OOP

-Design Principles and Best Practice -Coding Standards/Code Quality

-Programming Environment Tools

Symfony:

-Symfony3 - fundamentals

-Bundles, Configuration and Enviroments

-Doctrine, Databases and Relationships

-Symfony Services

-Symfony Forms

-Symfony Security

Acquired skills and knowledge:

symfony framework, GIT, doctrine, GitHub, javascript / jquery, phpstorm, bootstrap 3, php oop, phpMyAdmin,

Jul 2015 - Nov 2016

Book-keeper - Altex - Romania SRL

1 year and 5 months

Cluj-Napoca | Administrative / Logistics | IT / Telecom

Apr 2014 - Jul 2015

Assistant Store Manager - Media Galaxy Cluj Napoca - Altex Romania SRL

1 year and 4 months

Cluj-Napoca | Sales | IT / Telecom

- -general store management (representation of the company in relation to the local authorities, merchandising)
- -optimizing the store profitability
- -supervizing the visual identity of the store
- -planning resources (employees, working timetable, local budgets)
- -team management (task assignment, motivation, training, coaching and control);
- -employees selection and recruitment
- -sales reports

Oct 2009 - Nov 2013

Showroom Manager - Dante International SA www.emag.ro

4 years and 2 months

Cluj-Napoca | Sales | IT / Telecom

- -NPS (Net Promoter Score), Customer Care, Customer Satisfaction, NPS analysis, monitoring an optimizations at national level, customer feedback questionnaires, phone client feedback
- -Identifying new locations for expanding the showroom network at regional level, new location set-up, actively involved in personal recruitment, operational, procedural and sales training for new employees
- -General showroom management (representation of the company in relation to the local authorities, merchandising)
- -Maintaining a high standard of customer services, showroom image and solving unexpected problems
- -Planning resources (employees, working timetable, local budgets)
- -team management (task assignment, motivation, training, coaching and control); -employees selection and recruitment
- I have developed a strong efficient team for the Cluj-Napoca Showroom
- -I specialized in the analysis, monitoring and optimization at a national level, for the Customer Care/ Customer Satisfaction policies, based on the existing feedback system (Customer feedback questionnaires, out-interviews, customer phone feedback, NPS scores)

May 2008 - May 2009

Account Manager - Falmingo Computers SA-Flamingo Distribution Centre - FDC

1 year and 1 month

Cluj-Napoca | Sales | -

-achieving monthly sales targets

- -compiling, verifying sales reports to upper management
- -maintaining a good relationship with local authorities

Jul 2005 - May 2008

Store Manager - Flamingo International SA - Flamingo Computers

2 years and 11 months

Cluj-Napoca | Sales | Administrative / Public Sector

- -new location set-up, actively involved in personal recruitment, operational, procedural and sales training for new employees
- -General showroom management (representation of the company in relation to the local authorities, merchandising)
- -Maintaining a high standard of customer services, showroom image and solving unexpected problems
- -Planning resources (employees, working timetable, local budgets)
- -Team management (task assignment, motivation, training, coaching and control); -employees selection and recruitment

Mar 2005 - Jul 2005

Service Tehnician - Flamingo International SA - Flamingo Computers

5 months

Baia Mare | IT Hardware | Administrative / Public Sector

-warranty and post-warranty services, maintaining the store computers and network, logistics and merchandising

Education

2001 - 2006 College / Bachelor's degree - Universitatea de Vest "Vasile Goldis"

Marketing | Baia Mare

-no diploma

1997 - 2001 High School - Grup Scolar Tehnic Nr.1

Electronica si Electrotehnica - Electronist Tehnica de Calcul | Baia Mare

Skills

Skills from work experience

symfony framework, GIT, doctrine, GitHub, javascript / jquery, phpstorm, bootstrap 3, php oop, phpMyAdmin, PHP & MySQL, HTML5/CSS3, Programare PHP

Foreign languages

English - Advanced, Italian - Medium, French - Medium

Other info

Numerous sales trainings (Microsoft, Intel, Samsung, HP, Apple, Customer Satisfaction, Sales Excellence)

Driving license

Categories A, B

acquired on 05 Nov 2002